{
    "subject": "resource/Street_Warrior",
    "predicate": "ontology/editor",
    "object": "resource/Tricia_Gorman",
    "human_readable": "The editor of Street Warrior is Tricia Gorman.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9524678587913513,
            "question": "Is Tricia Gorman involved with the publication Street Warrior?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8975930213928223,
            "question": "What is Tricia Gorman's role in Street Warrior?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8332875370979309,
            "question": "Who is the editor of Street Warrior?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8161504864692688,
            "question": "Is Tricia Gorman a writer or an editor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7946645617485046,
            "question": "Name the editor of the publication Street Warrior."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7457239627838135,
            "question": "Who is responsible for editing Street Warrior?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7392789125442505,
            "question": "What is the name of the publication edited by Tricia Gorman?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6102288961410522,
            "question": "What publication is Tricia Gorman associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5194552540779114,
            "question": "What kind of publication is Street Warrior?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41084522008895874,
            "question": "Does Tricia Gorman work in publishing?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The editor of Street Warrior is Tricia Gorman.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5001_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What kind of publication is Street Warrior?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5001_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What publication is Tricia Gorman associated with?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5001_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the publication edited by Tricia Gorman?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5001_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5001_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5001_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5001_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5001_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5001_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5001_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5001_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5001_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5001_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5001_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you'd like to test more triples!  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe triple \"The editor of Street Warrior is Tricia Gorman\" is supported by the document with file_path \"/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_5001/re-ranker-msmarco/8.txt\", which states that Tricia Gorman was an editor."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe document at file_path /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_5001/re-ranker-msmarco/77.txt states that \"Cinematography was done by Yaron Levy and editing by Tricia Gorman.\" This supports the triple stating that Tricia Gorman is the editor of Street Warrior."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}